Hugo Serra

hugo.serra8@gmail.com (912) 555-4321

Richard hails from Tulsa. He has earned degrees from the University of Oklahoma and Stanford. (Go Sooners and Cardinal!) Before starting Pied Piper, he worked for Hooli as a part time software developer. While his work focuses on applied information theory, mostly optimizing lossless compression schema of both the length-limited and adaptive variants, his non-work interests range widely, everything from quantum computing to chaos theory. He could tell you about it, but THAT would NOT be a "length-limited" conversation!

Twitter neutralthoughts SoundCloud dandymusicnl

SKILLS

WEB DEVELOPMENT HTML, CSS, Javascript

COMPRESSION Mpeg, MP4, GIF

EXPERIENCE

CEO/President Dec 2013 - Dec 2014

Pied Piper is a multi-platform technology based on a proprietary universal compression algorithm that has consistently fielded high Weisman Scores™ that are not merely competitive, but approach the theoretical limit of lossless compression.

- Build an algorithm for artist to detect if their music was violating copy right infringement laws
- Successfully won Techcrunch Disrupt
- Optimized an algorithm that holds the current world record for Weisman Scores

VOLUNTEERING

CoderDojo

Teacher Jan 2012 - Jan 2013

Global movement of free coding clubs for young people.

Awarded 'Teacher of the Month'

EDUCATION

University of Oklahoma

Jun 2011 - Jan 2014

Bachelor - Information Technology

AWARDS

Digital Compression Pioneer Award undefined NaN Techcrunch

There is no spoon.

PUBLICATIONS

Video compression for 3d media Hooli

2014-10-01

Innovative middle-out compression algorithm that changes the way we store data.

LANGUAGES

English

Fluent

INTERESTS

Wildlife

- Ferrets
- Unicorns

REFERENCES

It is my pleasure to recommend Richard, his performance working as a consultant for Main St. Company proved that he will be a valuable addition to any company.

— Erlich Bachman